我這一生從未錯得如此過。
I had never been so wrong before in my life.
僅僅因為我不能分享我呼吸的空氣
For the fact alone that
I couldn't share the air I breathed
我那張逐漸下垂的笑臉就多了條煩惱的皺紋
brought an agonizing twitch
in my slowly sinking smile.
儘管這聽起來很荒唐，我哭了。
I would go as far as to say, I started to cry.
我也只剩下哭了。
And that's just what I did.
轉瞬間，我明白了，把自己關在這裡
Right then I had realized that trapping myself here
是個粗魯的決定，
was a rather rash decision,
而命運不會容忍我。
and would not be tolerated by fate.
我的朋友沒了，如此，我的笑容也是。
My friends were gone,
and therefore, so is my smile.
我向身旁的星星訴苦，但它們不回應。
I expressed my sorrow to the stars
around me, but they wouldn't respond.
它們甚至不知道我的存在。
They didn't even acknowledge my presence.
朋友會，但我已經沒有了。
Friends would, but I didn't have those anymore.
我又哭了。
I cried again.
風暴席捲，在這牆內。
The storm is raging inside these walls.
心上打的詰，終將打開。
The knots of emotion will come undone.
終將打開。
Come undone.